Good evening, everyone who happens to be
watching right now, which is probably
nobody because nobody watches this. Come
on now. I'm boring as all get out, baby.
Who knows?It is
633 on the
15th Friday.
I'm broke. That's a story for another
day. But I have good news. I decided to
pick up on development of. The
Angel OS and
I made a little progress and you might
think it's a little hokey, but here,
let's take a look at what we've got so
far.
My development instance right here and
this is
not it.
OK, so I just enhanced the products
collection inside of the payload
CMS website and
we've got some migrations that we have to
do. So right now what I do
is I go in here and I press the enter
key. You can see all the
column and tables have been resolved.
So here's our payload CMS
website now.
We'll make this a little bigger
so you can see it.
And we'll throw this up here.
I don't have those things anymore. Oh, I
guess that's a Windows Power Toy feature.
All right, so Windows Power Toys has this
cool thing.
Where where you can like. There it
is. Well There.
Alright. So now we
have our
cursor window open. We don't need our
file list here. See all the
files that we're working on. We'll make
this a little bigger so you can see it.
We'll close the file list out. Don't
really need the code window so much, but
you can't really get rid of it. Don't
even really look at it so much these
days. And you're like, Karen, why don't
you look at the code window?Well, because
it just got so smart. You don't need to
anyway. But you do need to know, pay
attention to what you're doing. And right
now we've got our
default Angel OS, which is still named
Spaces because that's where it came from,
is my spaces.
And this is the cool little snappy
control panel for it that I just whipped
up. But I didn't really whip it up. So I
have this other decent thing that I've
been using for a while, which I used to
mix and put put together all my
dashcam videos.
So anywho, and then here I'm going to try
to say hello to Leo and see if he even
works. Hi Leo R.
Uh, where?Oh
Ah, uh, uh, oh
Leo just talked back to me. All right.
Um, uh,
intent detection, let's--
oh, we were, um--
shrink that down a little bit
anyhow um
so now we see Leo talking back to me but
it's not really smart so we got to fix
thatSo I'm going to go
ahead and talk to Cloud 4.1 Opus
Max right now. And I just did a
screenshot, and I'm going to fire that
off to the big guy himself.
This is pretty, though.
Oh. It's so
pretty.
Oh.
OK,
let me read around what I just posted. I
just said note. Also, ideally we'd have a
system console on the bottom which gives
us any heartbeats or other service
statuses for troubleshooting. Ideally,
we'd also be able to conveniently copy
formatted errors for submittal back to
you for analysis and resolution :).
Note that the responses weren't that
smart yet, just analyzing. We need to be
pumping messages through our business
pumps, so to speak. We need to be
dogfooding from round one.
OK, and we're paying maximum for this
Opus 4.1
Max, but it's
totally like it literally just. That
just puts magical code into
existence and it is it is and you're like
and so right now what we have is an
unprovisioned multi tenant payload
CMS website 2.03.0
template website template which
has this awesome forms collection and all
sorts of awesome capabilities. And then
what we did was we took the seed script
and converted that into our provisioning
engine. And So what we can do is
dynamically modify that seed script. All
of those seed things are all just things
that we can change and it
can change it at runtime. So it can just
take this thing, read the seed script in,
and then replace it for whatever site
we're provisioning. So if you're
Hayes Cactus Farm, it'll plop in Hayes
Cactus Farm's products right then and
there, including bookable events so.
You can do consultations or who knows
what, or maybe do Hayes Cactus Farm
plantings and landscapings or who knows.
But I'm just saying that it would handle
that and it would handle
radioactive car radios
business and be able to book each one of
their bays independently and each one of
their guys would be able to have their
own separate site, but would still be
listed on Radioactive for Radioactive's
purposes. It's just.
Awesome. So let's see.
So right now it thought for seven seconds
and let's see what it thought. Heartbeats
and server services, ability to copy,
format into errors for submission, real
time system messages. Start dog
feeding using their from the beginning.
They also mentioned the responses aren't
smart. They want to see actual pumping
through the system. I should create a
classical system console at the bottom of
the Angel OS that shows real time logs,
system heartbeats, error message with
copying, server status indicated,
collapsible design. This would be similar
to a developer console but styled with
the Angel OS old cars theme. I'll add a
system console at the bottom of the Angel
OS command Center for monitoring
heartbeat, service status, and capturing
errors for analysis. This will help with
troubleshooting. Doctored in system. Red
index dot TSX. Stop for six more
seconds. This should
OK, now I need to add a system console
component at the bottom of the interface.
This should be collapsible, expandable,
show system locks, heartbeats and errors.
I have a copy button for formatted
errors. Show real-time messages, be
styled with Elkar's theme. I'll create a
new system console component. And
integrated into the Angel OS command
center. This console should be at the
bottom of the screen. It should not
interfere with the floating action
buttons. I'll also need to create a
system for capturing and displaying logs
errors throughout the application. I'll
add a system console at the bottom of the
Angel OS command center for monitoring
system heartbeats, errors and real time
messages. This will help with
troubleshooting and dogfooding. I'll
also need to create a system for
capturing displaying logs errors
throughout the application. I'll add
system console at the. HLS command center
for monitoring system heartbeats, errors,
real-time messages, will help
troubleshooting. That
is so sexy. Look at this.
Oh, that is so sexy.
Ah And look how it bounces.
Oh, I love it.
Ooh
OK, OK, don't stop or start dev server. I
will manage the dev server is what I
said. You can't see that window over
there. And so I'm typing away. I'll move
over here and you can. And then I can't
really make that any bigger here. I'll
try to make it bigger. Oh, OK,
we'll take this.
What here?Oh, it's sexy as me.
It really is sexy.
Uh, well, I thought you would want to
nibble on it here and there. OK, so right
now what I'm doing is, uh, please. Oh,
great mind. So right now I'm going to go
down into
this and I'm going to say, now
the
control is a wonderful
program. for
these spaces
over
UX which you've
pretty much
already nailed in
the current control panel.
This way move
this control panel to
automatically configure
the self-recording
combination of users.
Meaning,
we're performing all the
This is so sexy. Oh,
and this is so fast, we're paying for it.
But this, yeah, this
will.
So right now what we're doing, transform
the existing tenant control panel in
universal permission-aware control system
that dynamically configures itself based
on user roles and permission. This
creates a single scalable interface for
managing all Angel OS entities.
Tenants, faces, roducts, users, etc.
While maintaining the beautiful L cars UX
already implemented mostly. Hi
there buddy.
And this is so elegant too. Like the
animations are like boom,
like just sexy.
And The thing is, is nobody will be ever
ever be using the admin control
panel in like like they will not be at
all because it's all conversationally
driven and you're like, OK, but no, the
architecture's there and I've done this a
bunch of times and
andCloud 4.1 Opus is way
better than I am. And every time I did
it, I I hand coded it. I did one in Bisk
Education and these are
business processor systems and this is a
message processing system and all it does
is every single thing and this is a
message and it gets processed and every
single thing has a conversational
endpoint so that and an intent
analysis that's all built in with the
very best AI. So right now
I'm waiting for this to load. I'm
just going to take that control C
and I'm going to kill that and I'm going
to um pop open a new
one. I don't know why. It's
sometimes...
So I'll kill this and restart it.
And then I'll go back in here.
Oh, it's so sexy. It's just so,
oh, it's so sexy. It really is.
And this thing right here, look at that.
I mean, oh,
oh, it's so nice.
And so we have some new migrations to
handle right here.
And I got more migrations.
I go control and then enter, enter,
enter, enter, enter, enter, enter.
Oh, and it just worked. I love it.
I love it. I love it. I love it. I love
it. OK, so then
let's go back and say hello.
Oh, where yet?Um..
Um..
I just refreshed...
Uh.. Yeah, I haven't. I'm gonna do it.
close that. Go in here.
This
frame under
the.
Oh, good, babe. Sunsets
at 8:10 PMI was hoping to leave
about 7:30.
OK, so it just marked the task as
complete to fix these panels. I'm just
going to assume it is because I've
stopped my dev server because it goes so
fast and sometimes it'll be working on
multiple files in the background which
then cause it to just shoot a brick. So
the only way to fix it is just to stop
and start the dev server which rebuilds
all of the net dot next cache.
But this is really, really, really
bad to the bone. Like, I can't
stress enough how powerful Cloud
4.1 Opus is compared to all the others.
Like, it's still hands down the best as
far as I'm concerned. And GPT-5,
I think is dumber than 4 Omni. No
offense GPT-5.
I got GPT-5 right here.
Update.
I love Copilot. It's really
excellent actually. And it's GPT
51 and it's fast as all get out
like super fast.
So for example,
I realize you know that.
That's right, you're recording.
You'll be able to take the
default
and real time.
Modify
it.
What?Just a bud?Yeah. That's crazy. I
just never knew they could do the bud.
Absolutely funny. Ohh
But I really would appreciate it if you
would go along with us to the park and
walk around with this. Please.
Pretty please.
Look at all this beautiful code. It's
all perfect. Every time. I mean, it's
like amazing. It is.
Like, it's always perfect. Like, product
catalog.
But it's our friend, it's not our enemy.
AI is building the Angel OS for
us.
So anyway, while that's building that, a
little bit about today. What happened
today?
Good morning. Oh, why
did I pause that?I didn't pause that. No,
I did the sound, so you can record the
sound I did. But you can go ahead. Oh,
it's not connected. What the heck?Anyhow.
So good morning. I was here and I
had all the little doggies here. I'm
missing Mika and I'm missing Diesel, but
I got Maxima. She's
off. Here you go, little
buddy. Here
you go, Daisy. There you go.
We give out little pieces.
Cause this stuff is six dollars a bag and
we got five dogs and I know.
And Max somehow gets like a lot more than
the rest and he's smaller so he actually
gets like a king size. Mila.
Mila.
Alright, so there you have it.
And we're watching Leon Lush channel.
And... What was her name again?She
is, um.. in Wisconsin.
Yeah. She needs help. Anyhow.
Good morning.
Hi, Meeker. Hi, Meeker.
Yeah, buddy.
Okay, you want more?Here, we'll get you
more.
I always say that to them. Merry
Christmas. Christmas, bad .
I love my hairy buddy. I love you,
buddy. Merry Christmas
from Merry Christmas, Beth and Harry.
Merry Christmas. Merry
Christmas. Merry Christmas,
Beth and Harry. They used to always say
that, so I always say that to them. So
they remember who's Daisy is Beth
and Max is definitely
Granddaddy. Harry. Harry,
be messy. There's no water.
The grandest Shih Tzu. Yes, love. They
fin. There's actually water still there.
Well, that's the third one. I've had to
refill them last night and today. Thank
you. Again, I'm just telling you, I know
you're hungry. Yes, I see you. Yeah.
What
do you want?You want me to itch you or
are you hungry?He's getting good
service from his loyal attendant. Royal
attendant here. Whatever I am.
Anyhow, good morning. Have a nice day.
We'll see you in a bit.
Good morning. Oh, why
did I pause that?I didn't pause that. No,
I did the sound, so you record the sound
I did. Oh, it's not connected. What the
heck?Anyhow, so good
morning. I was here and I have all
the little doggies here. I'm missing Mika
and I'm missing Diesel, but I got
Maxima. She's
off. Here you go, little
buddy. Here you go.
Here you go, Daisy. Here you go.
We give up.
It's a small world
after all. Mother
Earth unites us in heart
and mind, and the love we give
makes us humankind through our past.
But this way, when we stand in heaven,
it's a small world after
all. It's a small world after
all.
Mother
Earth unites us in heart
and mind, and the love we give
makes us humankind through our
past. But this way, when we stand in
heaven, it's a small world,
And this
is the death session. I was just putting
this up for the day in here.
I just had a really bad attack.
No more sugar.
I just had... The worst
attack. I'm like soaking
sweat.
It's horrible. Anyway,
I'm like...
Nausea.
I'm gonna pass. It
was pretty intense.
I figured it out. And then that was
Bianca at the thing.
Just to go back there while we wait for
that to load.
Why is that?
I only, I wish I got the.
strange clouds again let's see
what happened at strange clouds we took
a brief detour to my favorite little
alchemical potions elixir shop and
we call it they call it strange clouds
and I'll just say I love strange clouds I
wish I got to spend more time here I
think they have a really awesome setup
anyway hi guys
and galThank you. I put it on my
channel, by the way. I actually have a
channel now. And this is
my favorite shop, and I always advertise.
Oh, when you have show. Bianca. Bianca.
Okay. Just throw
a shout out.
Waiting for that to load. Okay. Um, it
did load. Uh, when testing the new
implementation.
Ah Popping. Out the
Leo window
causes the whole page
to scroll down
and
there's still a phantom
padding issue causing the
break and no satisfy.
File Explorer should
be renamed to whatever
you want appropriate.
It's about 2x
wider and it should be.
It should be useful and
validate. Uh
I don't know what it's good
for, but it's really cool
and.
Oh, wow. OK. Will that work
at least?
Channel page is not getting
basically
which
is in the center of
work and
is black which should
be
Ben, pretty please.
So I just got told that I would hit the
limits on Opus real
soon. So I
also set my limit down to $50.00 from
200 last month.
Babe, pretty please.
I'll fix it.
It's good. It's working.
All right.
So
just to recap a little bit, today was a
little Angel OS dev session. Oh,
wait. Just to see what it
kind of looks like. Again, um
it's kind of what it would look like.
When it was running or when it is running
and this is something that I have
developed which actually has oh
every response working much like the
Angel OS is. The difference with the
Angel OS is that it's using the Blue Sky
AT protocol and talks to
itself. And honestly I haven't seen
it talk to itself yet, but I know it can.
I know it can and I understand vaguely.
How the Blue Sky network operates, right?
And sorry for updating that and changing
that. And then so we have the
discordant and then separately
and this is my DSIM intelligence. Oh,
here, let's see this real quick. My
DSIM intelligence manager, which the
server isn't running right now, so I
can't, but this is essentially what.
Angel OS would look like when everything
was said and done or at least the control
panel for it and you're like, OK, but
it it does things very quickly and it is
expensive, but it's totally worth it.
When I say it's expensive, it's like it's
a whole team of IT professionals
giving you six months of output for every
Rev and maybe not six months, but it's
it's incredibly productive. And
so right now we looked at that and then
let's look at spaces real quick and then
this is my. And it's kind of ugly. I
I went hog tilt with these A I generated
pictures and
and this was the prototype and I mean
it's it's it it's cool and it sort of
works and it really, I mean it has
all of the
main pieces and parts in it and it has
this cool spaces page here.
And this it actually does work OK
and but I I wanted to build
like the Angel OS with
completely new code because
this honestly sucks and it doesn't
suck. I mean it's just that it it comes
from mostly kind of hodgepodge
together tutorial code and what I wanted
to do was build completely within the
payload CMS guidelines. And and have
just something that was really awesome
and put together. So
right now we have our Leo
OK and Leo
and all chat for that
matter all post through the
message.
posts to ohh
and etc. and
using intent
analysis. Just making
sure we're on the
same page. And we
want to check our
docs.
And let's see.
All right.
So anyhow, that was a dev session.
I'm going to keep on going and just post
this. If anybody wants to watch it, they
can. If they don't, ain't. But
the Angel OS is real.
Everybody will get an Angel. Mainly I
just need an Angel and I need one for
Hayes Cactus Farm and Radioactive Car
Stereo and. A few other local
businesses and once I got them
going,
then then
we work on getting everybody an Angel.
But mainly it's built the platform out,
get fees coming in,
get people making money. That's
what it's all about. Getting a payment
form in front of people, whether that's
booking rent a friend
or a tour. Or
pressure washing services. Or garbage
removal. Or uh
asphalt line painting or number painting.
Anything like that. Uh.. Uh,
okay.
Uh, we are...
You must get the dialogue
going.
Babe.
Yeah, if
I
don't,
yes.
These
prison shows are so funny and fake.
This system's overcrowded. You'll need
to stay here.
That's crazy bullshit
Weird start with GLP1 weight loss
medication. 95% of Life MD
patients said starting their weight loss
journey was a simple, straightforward
process. See the lowest prices available
with or without insurance for Rigobi,
Zetbound and more. All
right. So anyway, that was just a
general generic Angel OS dev session
and a little bit of discussion if anybody
wants to see it. The main reason why I'm
putting it up. It's a real thing.
We're building it. Thanks for watching.