All right, good evening everyone. We're
coming at you from
HS Hangout, otherwise known as the Fifth
Element's lair. And this is the
consort to the Fifth Element and the
Fifth Element herself. Anyhow, um
I was going through the day's videos
here, and so I was going to
curate my day.
and I wanted to start with last night as
it were because it's really
cool. So I've got
this up here um
and this was last night I think
and we're going to pull that
up and I'm going to mute my mic here and
then hopefully unmute it once I get to
the end of this here.
Yeah.
Good Daisy.
Good evening.
Hi, buddy. Hi, buddy.
How are you?
Where's Matt?Come on, little buddy.
Come on. Hi, Tom. Hello.
Mika.
Max, come on, little buddy. Max,
this way. Yeah, that's
right. Come on, Granddaddy.
Come on, Grandpa.
Hakuna masala. What a wonderful
face. Look, buddy.
Oh, it feels so good on my feet.
Thank you, God, for this day.
Thank you, Mother God, for this day.
Come on, Granddaddy. Come
on, Grandma. Come on,
Grandmy.
I am actually speaking the truth.
Oh, it's so nice out here. It's perfect
temperature. I'll get Mika water at the
next station. Huh
The temperature is perfect.
There's so many different colors of pink
and blue in the sky.
Okay, Granddaddy wants something
that's different.
All right, Grandpa, I gotcha.
Map. Grandpa.
Good girl. Good
Mika. I love that doggy.
Good evening. Hello. How
are you?We are well. We
love this place. Yeah, so do
we. Three or four times a week we love
this place. Yeah, we try to get here
every day. I'm coming
up from Largo, so it's a little bit of
a... Worth it. Totally. Like the
whole reason to have a car in the first
place. We've
seen you guys here before. I I
oftentimes will post these videos on
YouTube. Oh. And I posted
about 11 or 12 of these dog
park lots of about the 50 that I have. Ohh
And then I have another-- 50
different parks?No. 50 from here. 50
different walks, peaceful walks,
or not so peaceful. But the
main thing is is that I have a channel,
it's called Clearwater Cruising
Ministries, and there is a
playlist on it called Enterprise Dog
Park. which is nothing but
serendipitous dog park interactions with
a whole bunch of wonderful people and
dogs and nature because
oftentimes they're just peaceful, quiet
walks. Were you here last year?I've been
coming here for
seven years. So are you familiar
with the owl nest that was here?Yeah,
vaguely. Do you have a general
idea of where it was?Ohh I just thought
there was an owl up there somewhere, but
I honestly don't know. That's a good one
to... I've been looking like every time I
come up here, because they got
a part in the nest. Normally I try
to respect guests and not like film
people, but I oftentimes film myself. But
no, I have, so I I post these
dog park visits that I do, and
then... I also, in the hopes,
mainly that what it does is like if you
have to leave your dog at home,
then it gives them a dog park experience
while you're gone. And not only that,
but an authentic one. So if you play
the Enterprise Dog Park, and usually I
try to keep my voice calm in the
mirror and... What's the name of the site
again?Well,
it's on YouTube. It's Clearwater
Cruising Ministries.
And we are actually a
Christian ministry. Well, although we
have to get our 4013C and all that other
stuff done. But we will be a Christian
ministry, like legally, actually. And And
mainly just kind of driving our soul van
around and and talking to homeless
people or going to pantries and
volunteering at like Florida Dream
Center. and stuff like that. Very nice.
But connecting people with like,
on the edge resources, essentially.
But, and dogs.
Anyhow, but yeah, and then we also drive
around, and then I have a home show on
it. And I'm building
something I call the Angel OS, where
everybody gets an angel, it's just a
really smart shopping cart. that can
configure itself as a
travel agency website for you. Or it
could be like a personal
consulting site or and it can also
connect you with with voice or whatever
and securely on your own private hardware
so that, okay guys, I guess we're not
going all the way around. We really need
to do a whole circle, but I'm following
Max right now and he he wins.
That's my grandfather by the way. I'm
not lying. He really is my grandfather.
Or he's he is the soul...
No, he is literally actually the soul
energy of my grandfather, Harry B.
Vassey. And tell me that is not the
harriest little...
And And Harry B. Vassey, I might add,
bars. But when you understand this little
guy, and then understand the soul
threads that connect him to my
grandfather,I'm telling you.
And not only that, but my dog
Daisy right there. No
lie. That is Beth
Bassey. I'm not lying to you.
I'm not. My grandparents literally
reincarnated as my dogs. And I'm not
lying to you. And I'm not crazy either.
I just...
This one does because I keep a very good
journal and... As a result of my
very good journal that I keep, I see all
of these synchronicities. No, I'm
serious. So I'm sorry I
didn't mean to mess you up. I found
my dog. Have a
blessed day.
But yes, Christians do believe in
reincarnation. This one does.
And Mother Gaia, and how important Mother
Nature is, and why I walk barefoot in
here to ground myself to Mother Gaia in
particular.
But that's the reason why I walk
barefoot, is to connect
with Mother Gaia. No, it seems to
be purple. Well, this is better and
easier, because it's just shells.
But we get that grounding energy coming
back. You have a blessed evening. I
didn't mean to scare you with the
reincarnation thing.
Have a blessed evening. I'm going to say
goodnight to Mother Gaia here.
Ohh Thank you, Mother Gaia.
And thank you, Father God.
Sorry we did not do a complete lap. It
did get kind of dark.
I kind of scared somebody. I didn't mean
to. I do that. It's
so beautiful.
Oh, thank you God for this day. I'm only
mean well.
What a beautiful evening in
Clearwater, Florida at Enterprise Dog
Park.
Thank you God for this day.
Yeah!
A song about enterprise door parking
Clearwater, Florida Where I'd take
Meeka Daisy and Max to play The
park is vast and when we walk We call
it our circle of life Or a
circle of life
Oh, oh, oh, oh, ohMatata,
good long Matata. Plainwater,
Florida, where I take a
easy and max to play. The park is fast,
and when we walk, we call it our circle
of life, or a circle of
life.
Good morning, everyone. We're at the
Florida Dream Center, which is the
firehouse on
56th Avenue, I think,
in Lillman, Florida.
And I used...
I used to volunteer here
for 300 hours, and not here, but at the
49th Street Pantry. So I'm just kind of
walking around. I love
this place. It's
been a while since I've been back, but I
really need to be back here, of all
places, because of a lot of reasons. And
I honestly don't know what I'm going to
find out. I do know
that I'mhere early and
late at the same time because they have a
whole team inside that's actually getting
all these boxes ready and I don't even
get a box or anything. So let's see what
we find out. Alright, and you can see
they're busy at work behind me.
Let's go ahead and clean the
entire... This used to be a
firehouse and
they have had this for a
long time. Well,for as long as
I've been living in
Pinellas County this thing. And
you can see, very
nice operation. Anyway, we'll be back
in touch momentarily.
All right, so another, a
beautiful morning at the Florida Dream
Center, framing and the truck,
and now we're off to the next stop.
where we're going to go to Leomin
or to United Methodist Church and see
what's going on there. All
right, good morning, Gunters.
We're at Clearview
United Methodist Church down here in
Leomin in in St. Pete area.
And I'm about to go do some traffic
control here, I think. Help out. I just
moved the Soul Van over. I don't know how
the Soul Van's going to be employed or
deployed. Definitely not going to be
deployed today. But we are
definitely really psyched about
putting on our black hat that
says Norminal so that we don't get a
sunburn.
Uh We do haveOur
normal, normal hat.
And I should have worn my Dream Center.
Thank you, Angry Everyday Astronaut. Not
Everyday Astronaut. Yeah,
Angry. I watch Angry and I watch Everyday
Astronaut. So,
right now, coming up on
this
big tent here. Boy, this big cupboard
here. Let's see how this is. A lot of
people don't like to be recorded, so I'm
going to turn it off respectfully at a
distance here and see what's going on.
Alright guys.
Hi guys, I'm with?Cisco.
Cisco with the Florida Dream Center, and
Colette already put me to work guiding
traffic, so I'm going to guide traffic
down here, but it's really filled up down
there, so we're going to have to move
them around up here. Cisco. Yes.
Alright, anyway.
So also, revenge on you. All
right. Thanks for watching.
Don't get
duped by eating the raw. Okay, real
quick, who we're about to see, his name
is Gary, I forget his last name, but
when I first got out of prison,
He was the guy that
had lights for me for my
bike because I was I literally
had $90 when my brother left me where he
left me. And so I was
totally broke and I had to go out and
actually earn money in order to survive
in where I was. Anyway, long story short,
one dude gave me a bicycle.
And it was like a yellow mountain bike,
which was too small, but fortunately I
was only 217 pounds at the time, and
so I didn't kill it. And then I only
had to ride eight miles each way to and
from work each day. But I didn't have
lights for the bike, and I couldn't
afford the $14 for the lights at Walmart.
As it happened, I was working at the 49th
Street Pantry, where I had to do
community service, thank God.
And that 49th Street Pantry was an
operation of Florida Dream Center and
Adopt-a-Block, which is a charity which
works out of Leelman, and it
helps all sorts of people in Leelman
area in particular. They work elsewhere,
but okay, hold on one second. Yeah,
okay. Well, I'm talking on this
real quick. So anyhow, that's
Florida Dream Center, and so, and then of
course there's Cindy Herbert who is like,
fairy godmother to so many people
and she just is like Mrs. Santa
Claus, if you will, every Saturday
morning, driving around all over the
place, crazy as all get out. Actually,
no, she respects all the driving loss and
stuff. But like more than anything, she
probably is more, well, there were two
things that inspired the Soul van. A, a
portable executive office suite.
that you can sleep in in a pinch that has
really nice amenities and it was really
inexpensive. But also because it's a
great ministry vehicle and it allows you
to go around and take the dogs and a
med's dogs and a med's girlfriend or
whomever, but we can all be comfortable
in the soul van and align our spirits
together and listen to some really
awesome music. So anyway, back to the
show. This is Gary, and I can't remember
his last name, but he's been
with the ministry with, well, with
Florida Dream Center for all this time, I
guess, and thank God because the guy is
just, he's definitely a guardian angel,
and he is and was my
guardian angel when I needed somebody,
he was there for me, and it was in the
most perfect way, in the most perfect
way. So let's listen to what he has to
say.
well Is there a festival coming
up?The women's events committee
that puts on the Christmas tree lighting
and the 4th of July event. We've got
an event in in autumn and fall this year.
The Harvest Festival, October 25th, and I
know that's a long way off, but if you
have any questions about the Harvest
Festival coming up, we'll be talking a
little about it, but those two can tell
you all about it.
That's going to be an evening event, and
that's going to be a lot of fun. That
starts, I think, at 5 o'clock. We'll go
talk to them back up.
I think that's all of the all the
announcements that I have. I do want to
share a scripture with you because I'd
like to do that.
3 says, By His divine power, God has
given us everything we need for living a
godly life. We have received all of this
by coming to know Him, the one who's
called us to Himself by means of His
modesty, glory, and excellence.
And I know there's times when I'm going
through trials and going through
challenges, got things in front of me
that I just don't think I have what it
takes to get through, or I don't think
I'm native enough or I'm sufficient
enough, and this isThis is
helpful to remember that that God has
given us everything, everything we need
to get to get through that. I hope that
can encourage you today.
Father, we just thank you for for your
words, a reminder today that that you
equip us with everything, everything that
we need to get through. And you are all
provided. We just thank you
for that. We just ask you to protect our
teens as they go out today, Father. We
just ask toare hungry, find one of our
Bottom of Life quotations, one of our
staff members, and just protect as they
go. And just thank you for your
permission. We'd love you to thank you.
Amen.
Hi, Gary.
That's Cindy driving the truck.
That is a cool van. You
know it's comfortable.
This is an awesome Savannah set up for
like ultimate living and
wow, this is
awesome.
It's beautiful and it looks comfortable
as all get out too. And you
have the overhead, which makes it a huge
difference. I miss not having that
actually. Yeah, I had, I
was about to buy one of these Explorers.
I'm gonna, they, they can find it.
There's one more spot right up there. I
was very close to buying an Explorer for
8,900. And the
deal fell through. I'm glad. That one was
only 45. But
I love what you've done. And you have a
portable AC in here?
I'm going to have to help this person
find a spot real quick. I'll be right
back. I'm scared.
And a half
hours of AC on battery.
Wow, that looks really cool. like you see
what I got, I got over here,
and we're not gonna do it. And this is
this is fantastic what I did over here, I
can show you on the back. And I saw on my
other van, they cut out a hole right here
for the AC. Look
at this, when I rent this air condition,
I'm gonna have to help this person. In
the winter time, I just open this,
put a piece of plastic over here, and I
have a heat and AC. And what kind of
unit is this?This is just regular air
condition, $200. But But the amazing
thing what I what i did... What
I did over here... You see,
I built... I built the thermostat
right over there, next to the blue cage.
Right. So when the temperature go
down, it go up, the
engine go like this.
Hold on a second. Let me help
this guy. Okay, they got a spot. Okay,
that's good. I don't want to get in
trouble for not helping. You see?
No, the engine start. When the
temperature go down like, like
it... And it is like .5 gallons per hour,
.25 gallons per hour on your engine?I
have 4.3. No, I just meant, what do you
think like your gallons per hour is on an
idling engine?Well,
in in two hours, gallon
and a half. Okay. Two
hours. It's a lot of storage room. This
is awesome. Thank you so much for sharing
this.
All right, well, it's about...
46 and the
Colette put me on parking
duty, so I'm helping out with parking and
and just making sure that
People move to the front here. We got one
open space.
But anyway, just enjoying
the morning and all the interesting
people coming through here. It's really
nice to be back or whatever.
I just had to take things one day at a
time, and but I love this place. Anyway.
Oh, this is so
cool. She starts looking around at these
friends of hers that got her here
somewhere. They wouldn't have just
abandoned her. They were so nice. How
could this possibly be?And she's looking
around and all she can see is just
darkness. And there's some moonlight
coming through the rear end over the
pond. But when she looked into the tree
line, it was just-- Can you pause it for
a second?All she can hear is birds and
insects, you know, night sounds. And
remember,
Now go over.
Buddy, buddy, buddy,
buddy. He's like not in your life.
Just itch him. He's like I do.
Yeah, I like that. Good Daisy. He's okay.
He's not gonna like it. That is
not somebody who would ever find herself
in this position. This is so far out of
her comfort zone, alone at night in this
forest, in this austere environment.
Suddenly it felt very austere and
terrified. And at the same time, her mind
starts telling her, oh my gosh, this
whole thing was a trap. Those five people
were . And so she's thinking, oh, I'm in
danger. I have to get out of here. And
she turns, and she looks at the trail
that brought them up here, and all she
sees is just this dark
cut path through the trees that's
basically pitching. And she says, I have
to walk through that alone in the middle
of the night. She didn't have a light or
or anything that would help guide her way
out of you. But as she's sitting there
panicking, she's thinking, I have to go
right now, like it's life or death. And
so she stands up and immediately she
feels really weak on her feet. She's
super fatigued still, but it's like
adrenaline is coursing through her body.
She's gotta get out of here. We love you,
Harry Bassey. We love you, Granddaddy.
I love you,
Grammy. I'm leaning on
Grammy right now, it's Daisy. She keeps
hearing noises all around her. We love
you, Grammy. Coming back to hurt her, or
animals, or she doesn't know what. I
mean, she's in full panic club here, but
just for hours, or what felt like hours,
she just stumbled through these trails,
you know, getting completely disoriented,
and finally she comes to the scream, and
she just stops, and she's sitting there
and she realizes, you know, the sun is
starting to come up. So she kneels down
and she scoops some water into her mouth
and right as the sun comes up across the
mountainside, there's enough light. What
are you doing?Hey, hey,
heyOhh I'm
sorry, Grande. Like
she's going to get out of here unscathed,
presumably. So she kind of catches her
breath. She puts another step from the
stream and then with the help of the
sunlight, she navigates her way to this
trail that she can see. Down the mountain
she went. As she was going down
she looked down towards her village and
she saw clearly there was a big group of
people, presumably villagers out looking
right down on the trail, sort of like
at the beginning of the trail. I love my
bud. I love you too,
Daisy. From the distance, I couldn't
really tell what she was or what she was
doing, but there was some level of
recognition, but she couldn't really tell
what the reaction of the crowd was, but
she had gotten their attentionFaye's so
excited, and down the hill she goes.
Suddenly she feels totally rejuvenated
because she's going to be okay, and she
gets closer to this big crowd of people
that she sees now. It's friends, it's
family, it's definitely her people. The
looks on their faces are not the looks
that Faye had expected. I mean, she did
understand that clearly I've been out
here at least for several hours. They
must have organized a search party,
they've been worried about me, but here I
am. like they gotta be relieved now
right they found I love this little buddy
not really sure
what to make a fake coming down the
mountain side it's just hard it like he's
just like a puppy and anybody else that
even thinks he's a puppy but like he's an
old man yeah I know man like look at him
he's not gonna
get any bigger he's not gonna you know he
has so much personality
walnuts on his brain
He's a multi-dimensional, yeah, but he's
a multi-dimensional........
They are special,
different people that have
you know, kind of made our way into the
mountains. I don't know, I shouldn't have
done it, but I fell asleep and you know,
here I am. I'm so sorry if I scared you,
you know, but I really, I'm okay. But
Faye's sister, it's like she was hearing
what Faye was saying, but couldn't
process it. We'll go to the store and get
some more, I know. Is
that feeling your arm?That has got to
hurt you, doesn't it?Yeah,
he has one right here, too. That's
not good. What is that?Appreciate that
Faye apparently... ...he has a problem
with him. Faye was crushed in the
water. I go get it out. Can I get that
out for you?60 pounds. She was horribly
malnourished, dehydrated. I mean, they
didn't understand how she was still
alive. And while Faye is being treated,
she did hear like what had happened over
the past... Oh, yeah. I'd say all right,
and he's like, Oh, yeah, all right. All
rightYeah. That showed when they went
into the woods, because she had on that
bright red-- Oh, they caught her walking
into the forest. There you go. Daisy,
good girl. I'm sorry.
Daisy.
Daisy, good girl. We love her
too, but Max is just so cute, you
know?And you know it, because he's,
well, Harry Bassey, Beth.
like Literally, actually. They had not
gone into any of the surrounding
villages, so she had to be
in the 18 Ponds of the Dragon Tank, that
seven and a half mile stretch. But
despite launching a huge search party
into that seven and a half mile stretch
to look for her, and also firing off
fireworks left and right to try to get
her attention, not only did nobody find
any of her...
We love you, buddy. We never heard or saw
any researchers. From her perspective, it
literally felt like she had just fallen
asleep for a few hours and woken up, and
here she was, not 17 days. But
eventually, they would actually go into
detail about the specifics of what she
remembered about this ordeal.
Mainly, she would talk about those five
people, her new friends, who sort of
encouraged her to go up into the 18
haunts of the Dragon King, and she
remembered their names, what it looked
like, she remembered discussions she had
with them, and she painted them as
wonderful people, butIt's like she just
woke up and they were gone. So she
thought, you know, maybe they had tricked
her, or you know, maybe they drugged her.
That's why she can't remember this stuff.
Or she didn't know what, but she couldn't
reconcile the fact that they seemed like
such nice people. Such a nice day
outside. It's just hotter than
Arizona right now. It's only like 94
degrees. Look, I see a bugger here.
I'm gonna get that attitude. It's just in
myThey've been dead for
a long time. And we are going out
shortly. They reviewed the security
footage which showed Fay clearly in her
bright red, distinctive coat walking up
the trail into the 18 pawns. There was
nobody else there. Those five people,
they're not on camera. So the 18 pawns of
the Mack and Faye is not justbeautiful
hiking destinations. It's also
made to look at the mountainside, but the
trail pass through and then ups the
forest as well. They sometimes see these
eerie blue lights moving around the tree.
There's a story that, you know,
people that have died, their spirits sort
of haunt this area looking for really
people to switch places with. In fact,
when Faye began coming down the
mountainside and she looked and saw that
hugewas basically, you know, a
search party out to vote for her. Well,
in reality, that wasn't the case. One of
the moguls had looked up and seen what he
thought was another one of those lights.
Oh, he's so cute.
Strange lights, a ghost, let's say. Okay,
I'm so sorry. Everybody was really
excited and it ran out to go see what it
was. It sort of was a ghost. It was a
fame. It had been gone for 17 days,
coming downAnd nobody could believe it.
They were so shocked. And so to this day,
nobody knows what actually happened to
Ben. All we know is we have it on camera
disappearing into this trail, into this
forest, into the mountainside. Righty.
Keep in mind, before
this, the longest anybody had survived
out there after getting lost was 12 days.
Hi, gang. Well, we're
out at Enterprise Dog Park on Saturday
afternoon, and it's just so beautiful out
here. We've got all of
the different insect noises, and they're
just buzzing and zzzzing, and it just
reminds me of my childhood.
All of the nights here and all the
cicadas out outside. And
And then you get out here and it's just
so peaceful, other than me
talking right now. But yeah.
Listen to that.
What the fuckWow.
So peaceful.
Hi, little buddy. Little
polar bear, I'm sorry we're keeping you
so long haired, hopefully we can correct
that soon.
Hope that Southpaw Dog Spa on
Drew Street in Clearwater will give us a
call back pretty please.
I was baker acted twice, just so you
know. I meant no harm. It
was completely out of my control because
I was assaulted by my neighbor, David
Rosen. Okay, so anyway, I've gotta go
right now.
So anyway. Alright, gang. This is
Stacey, one half of my ninjas.
There's Matt. Hi. This is Matt
and Stacey, by the way, hun. Hi. Okay,
she's gonna take Max back, I guess. He
wants to go back. I got it. But you can
carry him this way, too. Yeah, here you
go, babe. Hello, Matt.
Hi, gang. Well,
so anyway. All right, gang. This is
Stacey, one half of my ninjas. There's
Matt. Hi, this is Matt and
Stacy, by the way. OK, she's going to
take Max back. I guess he wants to go
back. But you can carry him this way
too. Yeah, here you go, babe.
Here and you can take this too.
I know Max we're going. Thank you. Thank
you babe. I love you. Thank you.
Keep that air conditioning primed and
cool. Ohh
It's Jax, right?
Your dog's name?Darce!
Darcy. Darce.
Darcy. Darce. Darce. Just Darce or
Darcy?Darce. Darce.
Okay. So, anyway, you're going to be on
my sixth installment. Actually, I mean...
Not that you really have a choice in it,
but... Anyway. No, so what
I've been doing is I've created a
new YouTube channel. called,
and I gotta get these dogs some water
here. We're going too fast. Let's slow
down a little bit. We're on a time crime.
You are?What are you doing?We have
friends coming over. Okay.
But, But so what I do then is,
so then on my home show, what I do is I
go through my Google Photos album, and
then I literally just pull these up and
play them along for them. But it makes
for, for me, like a really fun end of my
day, so every day I make my little home
show just about. And so I've got...
I'm building something called... Here,
let's go. Let's... I was just trying to
do the water thing, but I'm I'm a little
bit, uh.. So anyway...
No, I was trying to do the water thing.
I'm not trying to hold you up, but... It
is cool to see you. And any new movies or
anything?
No. Series. I don't know.
Wednesday on Netflix. I kind of want to
see it. And then there's also that one
with that wrestler guy. What's his name?
You know what I'm talking about?It's on
Netflix, though. You don't have Netflix.
Yeah, we do. He's like the Punisher. He's
like... But it's comical and fun.
He's like... He's the
wrestler dude that's not The Rock.
John Cena?Yes! John Cena!ohh But
yeah, it's a it's a pretty cool show, or
at least what I've watched of it. What's
our own bad gins, or--
we're going to AMC,
but not . But yet, generally
speaking, so what what my goal is, is
like, if I go to the dog park,
whatever I do, I'm trying to like
document as much of my life as possible
and profusely share it. You can't steal
what's given freely. Right?And I know
that sounds crazy, but it's like,
you can't stop the inevitable.
So...
Here.
The sound here is great. I was really
enjoying the piece, but I got really
manic when I saw you guys. So I was...
HuhProtest. Oh, I slowed down for it
and everybody got pissed at me. They
were giving thumbs downs. I was just
trying to read the signs. We thought it
would be funny to go get some
shoe polish. What were they protesting?
Trump. They were?Yeah.
Oh. Whatever, I don't know why. No, I
think they were all protesting different
shitNo, they're all anti Trump. Oh.
But we thought it'd be fun yeah to go get
some shoe polish because they got their
cars all parked there. Right. They were
like trumped for life on their car. I saw
some interesting things. I read
everything. I'm not going to like
exclude ideas. Come on guys,
Daisy, Darce.
But I'm not going to exclude
ideas like most of the lip
parts do, which is really interesting.
It's a word that my brother quainted or
that I first heard from my brother.
That's when I was, in fact, a libtard.
There's nothing wrong with being liberal,
you just have to be-- No, I just, but but
that was under essentially a different
paradigm, a different system entirely.
Right. There's nothing wrong with being
liberal, you just have to be willing to
talk to somebody about it. Well, the main
thing is is like I'm a total beneficiary
of like the government spending, right?So
like were it not for my VA disability,
I would be totally hosed, so I am so
gratefulto the VA and to
my to my civilization,
which has granted me this lease on life
that otherwise I would not have. But I
always thought what his cuts would be--
the systems were a little misinterpreted.
Like it was-- I don't know enough to make
an informed decision on that. Generally
speaking, everything that I know about
Trump is that he
might be the devil, but he's also,
generally speaking, pretty good. And
better than than Biden ever was.
And I kind of think of him as my naked
soul brother, actually.
Like genuinely, I think of him like like
we're just a divided soul.
He got the luckier like
plot in life or whatever, you know?
But thanks for letting me record this.
But I'm going to put this on the show,
and you can watch it if you want. Or you
can send it to people if you want. Or you
don't have to. Ohh So
what you been doing?Just hanging out?I've
been, so I've been,
at least my front room out to Ahmed, who
you probably know from here. And
Ahmed with the two German Shepherds,
Diesel and Mila, long haired.
He's always here, and his girlfriend is
Erica and she's-- That's the big dog that
carries the stick, is that him?Nah,
that's somebody else. But anyway, Ahmed
is currently renting my
front room, and then I have somebody
renting my back room, and I even have
somebody renting my front porch, who I
call Samwise Gamgee. Ohh And
his name is actually Ken. But it's not
even climate controlled, but he's totally
chill with that because he was homeless
for like two years before anybody would
even give him a front porch to put his
address at, right?How much did you charge
for your front porch?400.
Which is fair. And that really goes, I
mean, it's not like I live
large. I'm just disabled,
actually.
not extorting them. No, and
actually St. Vincent de Paul is the one
that's paying the bill, and I interviewed
with them. And I took an independent
survey of my neighbors and asked them how
much they would charge for a similar
space. And each one of them told me that
it would be uh more than that. I
thought you were in a condo. Yeah, I am.
Generally speaking, my landlord is pretty
cool.
No hard feelings.
So what, he's still doing this?I'm trying
to. Huh
I had a really manic episode like three
weeks ago because I have this this butt
head neighbor who I let kind of get the
better of me, but it was because he had
said something about, he said I was I was
a snitch and I didn't serve.
And when he said I didn't serve, I mean,
I literally get my income from my
be a disability, right?And so
I've never met a veteran in my life
who would like bespirch another and
say, oh, you didn't serve or whatever. I
mean, like I legitimately have tags on my
vehicle, but I got my-- The only
distinction I've I've ever heard between
veterans is like you could be a veteran
and you could be a combat veteran. Well,
I mean, my my ship was involved in an
international incident, which almost, I
mean,could have killed everybody aboard
right before I went aboard. Well, my my
grandfather always took issue with that
because he he was, he would
get, so he served in the Navy when there
wasn't a wartime. It was always wartime
in the submarine service. Well, always.
No, no, no, I'm not talking about you.
I'm just talking about you. Yeah. Silent
war. It's kind of a reverse of your name
you're talking about because he felt like
when people would give, he felt like he
didn't deserveLike his friends, they got
the same Vietnam and Korea treatment, if
that makes sense. You know what I mean?He
would say, Memorial Day is not for me.
I'm talking to you, I'm talking to that
person. Hey, come on, man. This is for
posterity. I don't even know what that
means. Posterity?Yeah. It
means that we're saying hello to the
universe. This This makes it up the--
Well, that's not the universe, this is
the universe. But this is an
amplification medium. And what this
does is, this sends out like this
massive, well, for me, this vibrational
joy energy out to the universe, where I'm
like silently going, Hakuna matata!
What a wonderful phrase! It
means no worries for the rest of your
days. So, that's what I'm
actually doing.
Is I'm actually saying, Thank you, Mother
Gaia, for this beautiful cathedral you've
gifted us. Thank you, Father God for
this perfect day. Speaking of
perfect day, guess what we're doing next
week?Ah, what are you doing next week?A
week, almost a week. Okay. We're going up
to Glacier National Park. I'm so jealous.
We're doing Glacier, Yellowstone, and
Green Tucson. I think
I'm gonna go to my brother's next week
and and go to Seneca Rocks or something
like that. I hope on Monday, right
after my job interview, ah
And then we're gonna... Yeah, I haven't
worked in a while. I'm really serious
about building the Angel OS, where
everyone gets an angel, even you get an
angel and you get an angel,
everybody gets an angel. But what it does
is it's like, it's like, did you
ever watch Transformers the movie?
Okay, now imagine Optimus Prime,
right?He goes, Ahh! and it turns in, but
they can actually turn into more than
just like their main vehicle, you know?
Well, that's exactly what I've
built. It is a multi-channel
everything clone. Yeah, we're going to
try... Which copies itself. We're going
to try and go right there. Okay,
let me see it on the... Hold it up to the
camera. Thank you, right there. We'll
talk to you. I don't know if we'll make
it. It's so awesome, but what you have to
do is you have to go get like a Hohem
iDroid gimbal mount. Right?
Dude! But I want
you to share that moment with me and
do it with a GoPro. Like
this right here. No, I'm serious. I'm
not dying. Because you
guys are so awesome. I would really watch
your channel if you had one like the one
that I have. Honestly, and I would even
plug your channel, if you have the one.
Yes it is to me. You're like some of the
most interesting people I know. I mean,
Matt is like a senior top
level Audi e-tron tech and
everything else. I can't even get a job
at his dealership, but this man's like,
it's the top dude in his dealership.
Actually, and I know it for a fact,
right there.
I'm going to do a different medium. We're
flying into Denver. Right.
Daisy. Where the magical mushrooms are
legal. They're legal here. It
depends on the kind. And since I've never
had an experience at all, no matter what
experience I have, it's going to be
great. Ohh But not
as great as the strawberry shortcake that
I got it purely right before I came here.
What?So, it
seems pretty. There you go.
So yeah, this is totally going
up. Bud, thanks for letting me interview
you a little bit.
No problem. What a beautiful
day, and then I missed out-- You should
be out there and interview some of them
Trump-- No!Good afternoon.
Thanks for petting the Regal one. That's
my daughter, actually. That's my
daughter. Hey, what are you guys mad
about?Here. So this
is like a single take.
I can't flip it around. I've got this pro
mode on this S23 going. What
are you driving up?Well, today it's the
Cadillac CTS.
3-liter performance, all-wheel drive.
It is a 4-door
Corvette powered by a
SwissWatch power plant. You got that
truck still?Uh, I got
the Soul Van. Oh yeah, that's right. Right
It's It's actually, I call it the
USS Enterprise. I'm
serious. It's the namesake of
the enterprise fleet. I'm telling you, I
am writing Ready Player
Everyone, where everybody gets
an Angel, sponsored by the Angel OS. And
I'm telling you, it's a real
thing. And once the Angel OS
emerges, it's going to
transform the economy in
really awesome ways. Because I don't know
how it's going to do it, but it's an
emergent ecosystem of
a Swiss Army knife,awesome,
top-of-class, it's
called a content management
system, which is called Payload CMS,
built on top of Next.js, which is like
the best development
framework for enterprises. So this is all
like top-level enterprise
architecture that can run on your
own box in your own office,
with your own models. And so literally,
actually, it's HIPAA compliant,
but and it can create any kind of
website that you need. If you need a
GoFundMe, it creates that. If you want
an OnlyFans, it can be an OnlyFans. If
you're a therapist, it can create a a
personal therapy. If it could create a
suicide hotline, it can do
literally, actually, anything.
Not a lot. And then I'm I'm like days
away from
a, what do you call it?
Well, minimum viable
product and so. But I have all of
these things working independently, and
I've built roughly 33 separate Next.js
sites, actually. And I have over
6,000 hours of coding and all of this
stuff. So, I mean, I'm deadly serious
about building the Angel OS, where
everyone gets an angel. And
anyway, Matt and Stacy. Good to see you.
Thank you so much for the interview.
And yeah, I am manic and a little bit
everything else. Have a great one.
Woo! Man, that truck is sexy.
Look at that thing.
Ah
Hello.
Come on, Daisy.
You can drive if you want, love. I prefer
not. Okay. I
just wanted to chill for a moment. Okay,
I'm chilling. It's kind of warm out here.
Jump, Daisy. Jump. Good girl! Ha ha!
Thank you, Daisy. Ooh You just laughed.
Did she call her something?Why are you
laughing
HuhHe took literally,
I saw a human characteristic and he
rolled his eyes and head back. Is he a
Uh.. No, she did
great. She actually made it on her own
power. That's such a
sexy truck. What?
No, I can't.
No, I'm fine, babe. I'm just a
little manic. No, I'm not manic at all.
I'm completely fine. I'm just having fun.
I just want to get that drive away. It's
so sexy. OK, I will get in.
All right.
A song about
Enterprise A song about Enterprise Door
Park in Clearwater, Florida
Where I take Mika, Daisy and Max
to play The park is fast and when we walk
We call it our circle of life
Or a circle of life And we
do our coon
Oh, oh, oh, oh Oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh Matata, Bula Matata,
Playwater, Florida, where I take
Meekabazy and Max to play. The
park is vast, and when we walk, we call
it our circle of life. Or a
circle of life And we do
our hakuna matata A
song about Enterprise Dog Park
In Clearwater, Florida Where I take
Mika, Daisy, and Max To
play the park It's faster when we walk
We call it our circle of
life Or a circle of life
Or a circle of
life
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Matata, banana, matata
Plainwater, Florida Where I take
Meeka Daisy and Max to play The
park is fast and when we walk we call
it Our circle of life, or a
circle of lifeAnd we do
our Hakuna Matata A
song about Enterprise Dog Park
In Clearwater, Florida Where I
take Mica, Daisy and Max
To play the park as fast and when we walk
We call it our Circle of
Life Or Circle of Life
Or Circle of Life And we do
our Hakuna Matata
We
call it a
circle of life, a circle of
life Along a mile,
enterprise apart In Clearwater,
Florida, where I take me to
Daisy and MaxTo play the
part is faster when we walk, we
call it our circle of life,
or circle of life. ... an
effect on why they can't really take the
punches as much. All right, we were just
watching Nexo Reacts. Anyhow, she was. I
was just watching this whole production
here. We're at an hour and eight minutes.
That's what I recorded today. Anyhow,
I appreciate anybody who watched that
with me. Uh It is
a beautiful sunset out and I'm looking
the wrong way for it, but it's still a
beautiful sunset. Anyhow,
thank you so much. And just a little bit
more. It's
uh right.
now 11 p.m.
8/16/2025
and we had an hour eight
minutes 49 seconds thanks so
much check out our original music
playlist um there's a
lot of stuff anyway we're just making
real authentic stuff real and authentic
have a blessed evening