Good evening, everyone. It is
Sunday, August the 10th,
2025.
48 p.m. or 19:48 p.m.
Eastern Time. Anyway, I'm
looking at some dashcam footage in there.
So this is a short update for the
channel, but I'm looking at some dashcam
footage. This is after... Keep in mind,
I was... I had just been
like threatened with my life anyway, and
I realize that for most of you, but I was
like pretty surprised that I was
so nonchalant about it given the
circumstances, etc. So all I'm saying is
this is oops wrong one here.
Okay. Uh, I think I've got that
down. Okay. Uh,
all right. So on with this show. Let's
check this out. Uh, I
gotta go over here... We call it
our circle of life Or the circle
of life And we do our
Hakuna Matata A song
about enterprise dog park
In Clearwater, Florida, where I take
me to Daisy and Max To
play the part just last, and when we walk
We call it our circle of life
Or circle
Bama Tata, Playwater,
Florida, where I take Nika
Daisy and Max to play. The park is
fast and when we walk we call it our
circle of life, or a
circle of life. And we do
our Hakuna Matata,
a song about Enterprise Dog Park
in Clearwater, Florida, where I take
Nika Daisy and Max.
Oh, here's my neighbor looking at me like
I'm all crazy, since I am all day.
To play the part, it's faster when we
walk We call it a
circle or a circle
That was.
I was in a lot of places. You understand
that Butthead Neighbor, like
it's been an ongoing day and literally
flashed the freaking knife in the sand
right right there on the screen. You can
see it's right up there.
And I literally had nothing. I mean, like
nothing. My Cadillac right there on the
screen.
No Navy.
I said, I ain't askin' You ain't begging
for peace Just don't lie to me and
reproduce Don't ever cease He said, no,
don't, but here's the curse You ain't the
monster yet, but you're rehearsed
All right, guys.
We wanted to get the whole thing in
there, by the way.
I was just trying to get an extra sign
sign. 'Cause my neighbors, they like to
turn their radios up all the time and out
the parking lot. And honestly, that
really wasn't that loud out there
compared to those radios. Nah, it was
nothing compared to the music. No hard
feelings. I was just having fun doing his
radios.
'Cause
there's other things, like the story that
I knew what my fifth element is, right?
Mika needs to go upstairs. That's
the best song ever. Now I just dedicated
that to you, but you can come out.
I'm taking Miko. Will you go with me?No!
I'm not coming back down here, please.
Okay, see you later, Alligator. I'm on a
mission. I want to go on a mission! It
is a perfect day outside. It is still
traumatized from her aborted sisters
that are living in her body right now.
And my aborted daughter. Yeah, that's
real. Hey, I'll give you three
minutes.
all twisted up in the three muses that
are the fifth element or my girlfriend.
All makes perfect sense to me. And if you
read my journal, you can pretty much find
out for yourself. So this is us talking
about before I go on the mission. What am
I going on?I'm going on a soul quest
here. I'm just looking for
somebody to quit Bika.
Never had a chance to go out with their
big brother.
This is down Drew Street in Clearwater.
I'm uploading this whole thing right now,
but it's really, really slow. And this
one's like 81 gigabytes, actually.
So, and and I wanted to get the whole
thing up because this is kind of like
group, but this is the trauma that
I was experiencing from that whole
assault from that weep shit
excuse me, that weep person that lives in
my neighborhood. that pretends to be a
former coach, even though
we see no actual evidence of it other
than the little placard on the front of
his car. Uh
Just pointing out
all our feelings are gone. Welcome to the
club, but all your
behavior is indicative of
not serving, as far as I
Anyway, let's just hope that
I'm wrong. And
you aren't like stalling dollars type,
but definitely doing a lot of
research on that point. You got a
lot of people looking at that, by the
way. I'm just a laden
young man.
We
got Easel, we got Liza, we
got Max, we got Daisy, we
got Mika.
They all fitting is so bad. It's kind of
hard to get them into the other one
anyway.
This is me talking to this homeless
person at the Serenity place in clearorder
here. Right here, look.
Uh oh.
All right.
So I ended up talking to this guy. He
wouldn't want to get on camera, but I
have been interviewing him at this
approximate time. And actually, we
could... And we can
look over at our,
um.. Ah, here. And
we're gonna go into here.
UhOh.
Refresh it.
It will take a while. Oh, there you go.
And you're wondering why I have that
here. This is the dogs.
Hi, Mila. How are you?
How'd you get here?
Hi, Diesel. How are you?
Anyhow, Mila and Diesel, there's
some med stocks. The med's staying with
us for a short while.
Also, I had a really cool little thing
today at Wally World. by the way,
before we get back to the other
thing. All is good. Ohh
He just, I don't know if he really wanted
treats or if he was checking out that one
chip. I don't know.
Look at him. He's intrigued. He's just
getting the bacon, but you got to make
them last three days, damn it. Tell
them that.
Hi. Here you go. Come here. All right.
Here you go. Cat, TPT said that that
was the stop Samsung app for-- Max,
what are you doing, buddy?Hey, Maximus.
Hey, Granddaddy. Hey,
Granddaddy, look at me, buddy. Hey,
old man. He's looking on the chick.
Max, here, I'll make you bigger.
Max, look at him. He can look. He
watches. There's a blonde chick walking
by, too, though. Yeah.
Here's Walmart here. If you can show the
treats on the on the screen, he'll look
at you. I bet you anything. Watch. What,
babe?Max, look. What's that?I've got
this. I'm working on this project. Is it
okay if I move these forward?Hold on one
second. All right,
so we were just-- Send anybody. That's
very sweet of you to say that to them.
Hi, I'm his first little girlfriend.
My name is-- I'm joking, sorry.
I can't tell right now.
I hope that I can pay for all this stuff.
Uh That's wonderful. Yes,
thank you. Pages
on Hawaiian bread.
I have a thing. Snack out. They're
here. I appreciate that. Anyway.
Next. Uh He's raising it up in the rain.
He raises it up, and he's got GPT hold
update with him. So this is our
neighborhood Walmart, and
Unique is not here today.
She's not here.
Hey. Whenever you do stuff like that,
sometimes?Just taking him on a tour.
Okay, got it. AI. Where
is it?I was taking my little guy on a
tour. That's it. He's in the car out
there. Ohh So, but this
is fun. So I put this on my video blog
in, like when I'm in Walmart, this
like serendipitously doing these like
little things. So when people hold up in
like a hundred or a thousand years,
That's why I do
it. And she's in the Cadillac up there.
Hi, little commander.
Commodore.
How are you guys doing today?
Ohh We're blessed in many, many
ways. Sorry.
Well, I thank God as much as I can on any
given day, a reasonable amount, but I
also thank Mother Gaia or
like, you know, we go to Enterprise Dog
Park, mostly is our
preferred venue for celebrating
Mother Earth and all that is wonderful.
I highly recommend that if you don't have
a dog that you get a dog just so you can
go to Enterprise Dog Park.
HuhWhere are you visiting
from?You know
Oh, and this is an Elon Musk thing, by
the way, in the journal. His room.
Whatever you want to call it. It was a
different- Yeah, Portal. Well, portal
would be the actual name. And I've been
so embarrassed to say it out loud that
everybody would laugh at me or lock me
up. You know, I
only told my aunt. So tell me what
happened. Something's not right,
something scary in that room.
Describe what you see and what happens.
I went to the edge of the doorway,
and I peeked in there, and I was afraid
just to peek. And there was
something happening in there, like a
sci-fi movie. And there was something, he
set him up like a little Stonehenge on
his bed, and he was tiny, like I told
you, so tiny. And he was jumping up and
down, and he was saying, Moon, come play
with my friends! Okay,
that right there says he knew exactly
what he was doing. It wasn't like
he accidentally opened a portal
and didn't know what he had friends.
So, um, I peeked in there. And I was
so scared. I'm embarrassed to tell this
I'm so ridiculous, like weird. And he
was being lifted, and he was starting
to go-- he was being lifted, and
like I was-- he
was being lifted
and being sucked in. I know
this sounds ridiculous, but my aunt told
me, don't let nothing happen to that
effing little--kid.
And normally, I would never let anything
happen to a child that was watching. I
would run between them in a pitbull. And
I said, the way she said it, I said, Why?
And she goes, She's gonna rule the world
someday. I'm like, What, Jim?What do you
mean?Why?And she said, Don't you know
nothing there, the Illuminati. She would
always do that to me, but she'd say,
Don't let nothing happen to him. He's
gonna rule the world someday. And I was
like, That kid?You know,
so I grabbed his little arm
and I got sucked in. I got sucked into,
it's like we went up and then we went
down and it was dark in there,
but it was glowing.
And I can only tell you that
whenI remember my peripheral
vision because I was afraid to look at
it, 'cause when you're a little kid, you
look at the cartoons and there's a bad
boogeyman in the Scooby-Doo, and you see
its glowing eyes. It's like, Don't look
at his eyes, he'll get you. And I
remember that, oh, ohh if you don't look
at their eyes, they can't get you.
And I was being sucked in and sucked
down, and I had his little arm, and it
was weird because there was no bottom.
And there were these creatures in there.
And they were giant, and they were
semi-shaped like humans. They were
glorious. They weren't like
smeagles or any creepy little demon
dudes. They were like beautiful, ancient
creatures that moved in a different time.
And they were giant.
And like they had a different head.
Like there was a bird head and like a cat
head and a jackal head. And
I would compare them because I'm not
super educated to like Egyptian type of
things. Okay, after
he did that opening the portal
thing, I didn't tell
what he did. And then I asked one of my
other, the head mother of the
Santeria, the head mother of the
Santeria. And I think she's the head
mother of those people that are Southern
borders, creating,
they're calling them in. Okay, they they
paid for this a long time ago. But I
said, is he the Antichrist?
And she didn't blink. She said, no.
But he won't present the mark. When you
see him do that. She said
that?She said that. The stage
will be set for the Antichrist to step
forward. So August 28th,
2020, Elon Musk presented the neural
link. UmmNow, is
the mark of the beast, the image of the
beast to be worshipped?Are they the same
thing?Now, I know how... Okay, so...
Just briefly...
I don't know, I just feel like I have a
synchronicity with Elon and I really do
have a new answer to life, the universe
and everything. It is 53 and I
can tell you how it's in my journals
anyhow. Hey,
Ahmed, you have the remote. I gave it
to you. It's a white remote. Ok, I was
looking for it. I couldn't find it. It's
very frustrating. You can play
Netflix. There is stuff on Netflix. You
can find anything on Netflix you want to
watch. Play it, because I have this. Play
it, I want to see Wednesday. I want to
see that. Here, Wednesday. That
looks cool, kind of hot. I like the
whole, kind of,Your
phone is playing. It's Call to
Prayer.
Do you have to hear it?
Okay, we're watching Happy Gilmore 2.
But I'm making a video right now, by the
way, just so you know.
So go back to sleep. Oh yeah.
That's Ahmed, by the way. He's from
Egypt. He's my, one of my soul
brothers. Anyhow, and I...
It's for a story for another day.
Oh, we were right here.
Huh
I didn't get arrested. That was bullshitI
mean baloney. It was baloney.
There's a med. Do you want to say hello?
I can't. I'm back. I
know. Very true. So this is
me driving through Clearwater right here.
Look, driving through Clearwater?I'm.
Look at this. Ain't a reason
that I see it now in this version
That's our production bite. No, that's
the whole point of this show. We're in HS
Hangout, or in this case, we're in
Wayne's World's Hangout. We're in the man
cave. Mostly, man cave.
Now note this guy right here was holding
this. And he was there for like
days. I need to go back and see him and.
So the goal was to bring Minka out with
him, if you can hear me over that here.
Okay, so here I'm just hanging out with
the old man out there on the shore there
and um
I mean on the sidewalk there and I kind
of sat there from
right the time stamp right here
is 1:40:11
so I go from 1:39 I
spent all this time just kind of hanging
out with them here on the thing.
Just watching all the people walk by.
Ah, nobody. Oh wait,
here.
Okay, so I was making a royal fool of
myself. Look, Look at this, this is me in
downtown Clearwater. This guy's just
playing with his freaking baseball card
collection.
Look.
I'm trying to find anybody...
Cheers! I missed
out... Angel... Okay...
I met Norm...
What's the new rule?If you find that you
need them in any limits, not
requirements. I always drive fast enough
not to piss anybody off, but sometimes
I'll turn
that way down.
All right. Oh. Oh, I
love this.
Okay, here we go. We're going across the
bridge. Let's get me out of the way here.
I look up with you. I go,
uh, it's so pretty.
It's so pretty.
ohh
It's on a really big screen in front of
me, which, it's almost like
being there.
This is my original song, by the way, I
wrote it.
Oh, ohh this whole video is viewable. You
can go fast forward or rewind through
it to your heart's content.
Keep in mind that I was a little nutty
and not just manic. Not like, like
literally actually manic, okay?And I'm
still kind of manic, but not really. I'm
mostly tired because I got the crap beat
out of me in jail andDon't
learn feelings.
I mean, there might be a lawsuit
training, but mainly just for the foot
head who put the knife on me in the first
place. That was the wrong move,
buddy. That was the wrong move, because
there's like a statute of limitations,
so any time they can, I mean.
Multiple witnesses saw you pull a knife
on me with my hands behind my
back and I wasn't even threatening you
dude at all
Why you would pull a knife on me and
threaten my life no less
That's Literally actually assault with
a deadly weapon. It's a It's a
second-degree felony
Just sayingThat's the actual
felony that you perpetrated on me,
sir. Not to mention the felonies I
saw you perpetrate on my next door
neighbor. And I'm just reminding
you again...
I haven't forgot. This is the
victory lap for that. And I spent a week
in jail because of the mania I got as a
result of your dips...
And I'm just trying not to say anything
unkind.
But as far as I can tell...
Yeah. I've never met a former
service member that would behave
remotely like that high head. Dude is a
straight up...
Watch the new world grow. And I tried
to frame it like, you know, he's got...
Like good shepherding skills or he's a
good shepherd, but he's got a tight ship.
But I mean, the guy's a helicopter parent
with his dogs and his dogs are vicious
and really did attack another park goer's
dog. And yeah,
I did identify him because that's what
any good citizen would do. If their
dog attacked another dog. And you know,
my dog was attacked once just recently in
the park and everybody's like, why didn't
you?I was like, cause the kid was 25 and
I didn't feel like ruining his day. And
if it was me that was bent like that, it
would be like a four alarm fire. But
Daisy's a pit bull, sort of. And
while she didn't instigate it and while
it hurt. There was no hard feelings in
that kid and and the dog, whatever. But
in the case of Shredder, this David
Rosen's dog, yeah, that dog is
vicious and it
did bite another dog at the park and I
was not a part of it at all. But I
observed this guy's a menace in
this place and at the park, wherever
he goes, he is a menace and he's
got anger issues out in the wazoo.
And I just can't believe for a moment
that those anger issues have anything to
do with actual service in
any armed forces of this United States of
America. Correct me if
I'm wrong, I put my DD214
up on this channel so you can see it and
I'll block it out to you. I've got it in
my bag, all my certificates, everything
else. I'm not anything
special, but I'm pointing out that this
whole thing was instigated by that
butthead. Straight up. That's the
whole thing that started this. And yeah,
I let it do it, but I'm also a veteran.
You know, I'm also, like, I don't believe
I'm entitled to anything, but when
somebody flashes a freaking weapon in my
face, instead of listening to me say,
yeah, I'm actually a veteran, I mean, I
can literally pull it up on my phone, but
you're. Flashing a knife in my
face again. He had a knife in his
hand multiple witnesses saw it This is an
accusation It's all I mean I
have all the timings and everything the
guy is yeah, he's a loose cannon
rolling around our deck That's a
fact I'll point out that
this was the day before Hulk Hogan died
and I'm going like two miles an hour
throughClearwater.
Yeah. You know what?Because Hulk Hogan's
a great man. I did not know he was going
to pass away that night.
But this is literally the day
before he died. And this is
his
shot right here. And it should be into
the Hulkster right here. Though we
haven't changed to the whole... Can
you hear me?Yep.
I got you.
I did a slow-bo drive-by.
Slow-bo.
And I wrote this song.
Now I'm really serious. Why is this
guy... I
really am actually bullish. And you can
say it every once, but I am bullish.
And I've broken it.
And when I say I've broken it...
So many hands have been broken on stiff
skin.
Yes, a lot of pants.
I'm not the best fighter, but I've got
the hardest bones.
Yeah, look at this. One more round.
Now I'm not gonna do that again, because
I'm weird to build this track, and
hopefully I get it fixed this morning.
OK. And I'm
lazy talking, all right. Now,
you can find this is in the Soul Bus with
the crashed windshield. That's where I
used to work right now. That used to be
the holiday in Surfside. I used to deal
with David Jermaine
for a short while.
That's the holiday
Okay, let's keep up fast forward. This is
a lot of time. Okay,
fast forward. Ohh
Got the spirit
turning right inside No sheer
of shame can stop
this rise
This is the best beach in the world. It
really is. And I love you guys. I just
want to make sure that you didn't miss
me. I'm back! Just
making sure. I'll be back a few more
times. One
more time! Hey, Icor!
In case you missed the last one. It's
very super easy. It just takes a lifetime
of
like.
RPE Soulcast blog is here.
You can see my Genesis program.
Like whatever, whatever, whatever. But
the point is that I am legitimately a
born atheist.
I'm sorry about that. I'm
legitimately a former atheist and I am
legitimately a born again Christian
hallelujah and I do not
subscribe to anyoneBut I would
very much love to be able to
bury the hatchet, which never existed
from my side for Rodney. But
apparently these guys don't return calls.
And when they did return calls and I was
like, I am, she promptly hung up on me.
No hard feelings. Again, I am
legitimately a former parishioner of your
church. You did trespass me. It didn't
cost me $717.20
in impound fees. As well
as $100 bond for that, plus
court fees, plus a lot of pain
from having to actually physically walk
around for 32 more hours in a cell
in the in the inappropriately
assigned ghillie suit or what you would
call the turtle suit. Yeah, so that
was really effed up, you guys. Just
saying. I literally went there. I showed
you that in the last video. I'm not going
to go back there again. Rodney, I would
really appreciate it if you would give me
a call. 727-256-4413, give
me a call.
727-256-4413, give me a
call. Please. That's all I'm saying.
You give me a call. Every single thing in
that movie happens to you. Or anybody
else. I might answer it or I might not. I
mean, I, what do I care?
Ohh So this is, but here's where it gets
better.
Okay, here's me getting pulled over by
the entire Clearwater
Police Department and this will be on cop
cam somewhere. So please pick it up.
And the whole point of this was actually
to marketReady Player
Everyone, massively multiplayer online
role-playing experience brought to you by
the Angel OS, which is not just
a thought, it's actually a
GitHub repo at
github.com/the-angel-os.
Yes, that's what this is all about.
This is me getting pulled over by the
entire police
department.
What's up, sir, how you doing?Uh, blessed
by God, sir. We're just making
sure you're good. I'm good. You got a
crack in your... I can't really say or
you'll think I'm crazy. Are you diagnosed
with any mental
health disability or anything?I'm a 70%
service disabled veteran. Okay, do
you suffer?Okay, let's
see. Uh, right. I'm diagnosed with PTSD
and several other things, you can look it
up on my record. All right, do you take
your medications and all that?Always. Are
you feeling okay?All right, have a good
day. All right. Do you have your
driver's license?
Of course I do. All right. All rightHow's
my sex offender registration thing right
here, too?Would that work for you?If I
can see your driver's license?Yeah, I'll
give it to you. Thank goodness I still
have all that now. You want to hear the
sign rep?Brady Judd?
Yeah, they wrote a song. Brady
Judd, it's true. I'm trying to remember
it. That's why I'm driving around singing
it. Yeah, but what I can
say is I'm his biggest fan.
Frequently. I am. I listen to his
words all the time. And it that's my
fifth element right there. Ohh
Quite funny. I've got him somewhere. He
generally speaking has some very good
wisdom to a part along. That's nice right
there. Oh ohh wait!
What do I have in my pocket?
I have a piece of anchor! In this case, I
had a cracked windshield. Right. I didn't
mean to do that. I was mad. I can't speak
around it. So when I get crazy, I look at
my anchor and my grandfather, he's
sitting right there. Uh, and I had
his glasses on, but they fell off when I
went to the church last night. And...
They didn't let me in. No hard feelings.
My name is Kenneth Court, or you can call
me under ratings. Yes, sir. Do you have a
driver's license cashed?I sure
do. Oops. Episode on the television in my
apartment.
Because... OK. Alright.
Speedway now, but when I was here. I
can't look at that. I mean I just, I was
useful. I was really goofy. I
was really good. Once you realize it, and
then you realize.
The glasses I left at the River last
night, and I'm not lying, I'm not, I
swear, I I love guys Rodney Brown,
Rodney Howard Brown, very much,
andOne of the reasons why I love him is
'cause he's a mustard seed, apparently.
Because he anointed me personally. I
don't even know our feelings. I would, I
am, I am this year and it was the best
effort to. And oh my god, I
mean... That's how!
Man, this is a 71 piece. Thank you, God,
for that one. But I will point out,
there's a whole lot of dash campingother
video for those channels that like that
stuff go get it because it was
really great I thought I did
particularly well in my role
and you know perhaps
you might agree that strange things
actually were afoot at the Circle K and
I actually made them afoot at other
Circle K's just so you know
and uh anyhow
I skedaddled out of there
without raising a ruckus.
You must stop.
Ah, and then shortly thereafter I got
beaten up by Officer
Jeffrey Williams of the police
department. No harm failings, sir.
did just get a salute from me a couple of
minutes prior to that I'm pretty sure if
I'm getting that right. Anyhow,
so that was the big day
and that's what I'm uploading here where
Strange Things were afoot if they're
Circle K. Ah
And
then we have Brother Ken,
Samwise Gamgee come in.
Oh goodness. Samwise. The rest of the
story. Yes, well I'm making a video right
now, Samwise. How's it
going?Ohh Well, I'm still making it
while I'm finalizing the other one. Are
you the big dog that scared everybody?
And again, this is the ministry and we
are not asking for anything. We're just
sharing our vision of
Angel OS and
the upcoming release of the
Angel OS
and our
ministry of going around and like
hanging out with people that don't have
anybody with our dogs and going to the
dog park and looking at the sky
mostly just enjoying
driving our favorite Cadillac car
or our favorite soap van which
Chevy Express 1500, 2000 with
233,000 miles on it. But
we love ministering to people and
however we can, if that's just hanging
out with them, maybe giving them
something. Hopefully we can bring
some baseball card sleeves back to the to
the guy downtown Clearwater. He's
83 years old, he's been there for like 20
years actually and he'swas a carny for
24 years and he's from
Kentucky and but I can't remember
his name off the top of my head right
now. Anyhow.
Ah And here's another nighttime scene of
downtown.
I love Clearwater
HuhI've been
here all my life I love this
place It's my
favorite place in the world I'm glad I
get to live here instead of anywhere else
HuhDid you
go to Clearwater High School?
Park High School. Okay. Morgan
Fitzgerald Middle. Park Flight
Elementary.
Yep, a lot of things change around here
for three years.
HuhDo you ever want
to hear God laugh?Uh,
I hear a guy laugh when I laugh.
These dogs really want to go outside Ken.
Can we help these dogs go out?Uh,
get them on the leash?No. Ahmed needs to
take them out. HuhAhmed needs to take
them out soon. I said get them on
the leash. Then you can control it.
Believe it or not, I think Rich just took
his chihuahuas now.
Yeah, Rich is getting on my last
nerve.
don't do the thing, you know
He just came out the door and seen a big
German shepherd, you knowAnd then he
spent five minutes yelling at me about
it. I was like, okay.
And anyhow. I
mean, it's just a big misunderstanding.
You didn't, but the idea is when you got
a dog that big at the apartment complex,
You have to have control over
it. Uh, it's not my dog.
Thank you.
It's on, it's on buddy.
It's not on me. I mean I, I realize that
like I let him bring the dog here but.
But
They're his dogs. When they go out
that door, they're out of your your
apartment. Uh, this is our apartment now
buddy.
They're not my dogs either. That's the
point I'm making.
Because they're Imed's dogs.
Imed's dogs. Oh, that's the guy over
here. is here right now and he's sleeping
on the couch.
Um Except for one thing.
My problem in this case is that Rich is a
fag number one. And number two,
no, but the separate issue is that his
dog's on a leash and he's the
last person to be telling me that.
it doesn't matter these dogs are timid
and they are I've known these dogs
for years right
right
and you bring up very good points brother
in Christ you do and I
tend to want to agree with you
but him yelling at me
right and and like I said so if he wants
to yell at me then he canhear me yell
defamatory things that are
absolutely 100% true about him and
his complete lack of character. Because
he is a total woke bleeding
homosexual. And that's a factual
statement. But that's his life, I can't
control that. No, I'm all about having
diversity of thought around me. I am
totally about having diversity of thought
around me. But, I...
I will disagree with that
and I definitely believe in no
buts. No buts.
Anyway, you know that. Did you look at my
Facebook when I posted?No, I don't have
Facebook. Oh, okay. I'll show you a
picture and then I'll tell you. As a
matter of fact, I just sent it to you. Umm
Tell me what you see in the picture. I
was sitting outside and I took it.
Well, anyhow,
here's a wrap right here.
Uh
Anyhow, that'll be all for this
week, I guess, for the time being.
Uh, we're at 5430.
Alright. So,
without much hoopla, that'll be
this update. I hope you have a great one.
Thanks for watching. If you did.