Good afternoon, everyone. Today is
August the 14th, 2025, and the
time is currently
54:47 p.m.
And, of course, I have my brightness set
up way too high, so it makes it very
difficult to see that here.
Let's check that out. Ah, nice
little clear water cruising.
You get a good idea. Our temperature is
87 degrees. Got outside. Beautiful day.
We had an awesome adventure. I
just made a little clip of myself
making a fool of myself
with my favorite song
ever, Enterprise Dog Park,
or a song about Enterprise Dog Park. So
without further ado,
Two, I'm going to start out with this
song about Enterprise, a song about
Enterprise Dog Park, but I'm not going to
play it off of this right here, the this
version. I'm going to play it off of the
version that I just made for another one.
Anyhow, let's try this out. So let's
listen to it real quick and see how this
goes. I just listened to this one myself
and I. like, it's fun. But then I
realized that most of the time when
you're doing a recording, you're going to
do multiple voice tracks, and honestly,
my voice is a little messed up right now,
but I feel like I still have Dave's
voice, like, because I've got Dave's soul
also. Adrian, I'm telling the truth.
All right. So, anyhow, that's the reason
why I cried so much. I couldn't help it.
Because I'm David Lam- and or LeMay and
kept recording, and you don't need to
under- anyway. So, without further
delay...
Let's see what's up. Raggy.
Ohh All
right, we're doing mic check two. Let's
see what happens. I take some gains and
stuff, so let's do it.
Okay, one more time. We're doing a
karaoke mic check. Karaoke. Enterprise
talk party. Clear water, Florida,
I take me easy. And Max to play
the park is fast and we call
it. A circle of light, over a
circle of light. And we call it
a .
Whoa Whoa
Whoa
ohh
a
circle of life for a
circle of life
a song about enterprise
to heartI can't
meet the raising air masks. We
play the part 'cause last the soon we we
walk. We call it a circle
of life, or a circle of life. A
circle of life.
When do I have to
Whoa, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh.
Songs about... If you've never
heard of Florida, take me to the
easiest path to play.
That's where we walk. We call
it a circle of life, or a
circle of life.
Oh ohh yeah! I love that
song! Thank
you so much for letting me share that
with you. If you watch that along, we're
so grateful. All right. And then we have
such a treat today because Harold and
Kumar got to go to White
Castle. All right, so let's shut this out
real quick and we're gonna go intohere. I
think we finished up our coffee process,
we should be. All right.
Umm All right, let's check this out.
Harold and Kumar, or rather
Ahmed and Kent, are pissed
at each other 'cause a man locked us out
of the freaking soul, man. And I'm so
angry. Me too. Ah
He's like, what do you mean it
automatically locks when you close the
door?I'm like, the thing has got a stereo
system from like yesteryear.
It was like $20,000 stereo system.
So anyhow, now
we have to walk over to John's
auto shop, who's got his son, hey
man, keep it going too slow.
So we have to walk over to John's Auto
Shop and meet with Ben
and we got somebody coming by. What's up
buddy?How you doing man?
Alright. So,
woo! Ah
How are you
guys doing today?My name's Ken.
What's your name?
Anna. Anna, and what's her name?
Joe. Joe. Yeah. Hi, Joe and
Anna. I'm Harold, and this is Kumar.
Actually, it's Ahmed and Ken.
We're going to White Castle. Just
kidding. We're going to John's over there
because a med doesn't realize that you
never close the door of a vehicle
when it's running. Because if
you do, it might lock itself.
So now, we have to go talk to
Ben, who is our best buddy
from Enterprise Dog Park, I might add.
True. Because we both met at Enterprise
Dog Park. And so,
anyhow, it's all good.
I said some very loud words, but they
were well-intentioned,
actually. You guys, we'll go this way.
We'll take this one and then we'll go
this way.
All right. We have 23,
22, 20 here.
All
right. So we make a
soul quest out of this, right?So
we had to leave my Fifth Element, who's
my girlfriend, and also the hottest girl
in the universe, something like that,
back with the Soul Van, right?
And now we have to walk here to get this
special part so we can unlock the Soul
Van and get back to our journey and our
mission of helping the people
who are in food deserts and
need assistance or who haven't had a
dog in a long time. well
Just need a ride to the food pantry.
Because that's why we got the soul van
for it. So. You said your name was
Eve?Oh,
Anna. Anna. All right. So we're going to
put this on the show tonight. And
so I have a show. And it's episode four
that's going to be on tonight. And it's
Clearwater Cruising
Ministries.
Ministries. because we
are like a Christian
organization that is Christ-focused,
non-denominational,
but definitely
God-fearing.
Clearwater Cruisin Ministries.
Let us walk across. All right, here.
Ooh I'm manic
right now. I had such a great
day, though. We went to the dog park.
and then um we got the
soul man out of Safelite Auto Glass
because the deflector shields otherwise
known as the windshield
got damaged when the fifth element
threw her transceiver device at its
swift flick. It was horrible
but we're getting it fixed and you have a
good one Anna. Anna?
Awesome! You have a good one!
All right.
This is fun. Held
in Kumar, go to White Castle.
Yeah! And see,
he is not single, ladies. This
man is taken.
Not me. Not me.
Not me. We know who your soul flame is.
Ah Anyhow.
So we're going up to see Ben here.
And we're having fun doing this.
What a great way. So here's another
important lesson.
Always turn a
disadvantage into an advantage.
And right now, what we get is extra Soul
Quest points. Because as it
happens, we're going to get to meet Ben.
Gesundheit. Gesundheit.
Gesundheit. HuhI said
Gesundheit.
Oh, ohh look at the plane. What an
awesome day to be locked out of the van.
Where is it, look at it?Right up here.
And you can send this to your brother.
Seriously. Hey brother,
what's up Mohammed?Hey, what's up?How are
you today?We're having
an advent shot. Woo!
All right.
And you're going to break a
lot of hearts. I wish.
You have broken a lot of hearts. I've
broken a lot of hearts, and I'm sorry to
all of them. But I have given
my heart to my fifth element, and she can
have it any moment. But
she's my mother Gaia also,
and everything else, Aphrodite and
everything. No hard feelings.
How are you today?I am
awesome. Glad to be
alive. With my best
buddy, Ahmed. That
is hot. Look at that.
That's nice.
Alright... Ben is so cool, and John is so
cool... They save me so much, and
he's just awesome, they're just great
business...
Honest and integrous... Hi Ben... Ah
So, we're over here at John's Auto Care,
and we're speaking with Ben... I
signed him. How you know him, man?Yeah,
we used to hang out at the dog park. How
are you doing?
You're walking here. I don't know
that. You know, I
walked out from the van, and just
in the van. It's a small world after all.
It's a small world after all. It's a
small world after all. It's a small world
after all. It's a world,
but it's a world. This is so awesome.
What a beautiful day. Right here in
Clearwater, FL.
This is going on my show tonight. I hope
you don't mind.
I promise, Kevin... HuhNo, I
don't. Oh God, I got it. Bump it up, and
you use this big stick, put it
in there. Is
this your ride?yeah It looks like a lot
of fun. My name's Ken, by the way.
What's your name?Ken. I'm Chris. Chris,
nice to make your acquaintance. These
guys are awesome. Yeah, I just, I had a
light pup on the dash occasionally, and I
just got on the gym. They come
out, it used to be they go off,
but we didn't let them check it out.
Yeah, well all I know is I've known this
guy for like ever from the dog park, so I
know these are the best guys around. yeah
yeah this is like we're very lucky to
have these guys here we'll be right back.
I usually go to Trent and stop but you
know I'd rather find a small place.
They saved me a ton of money on my
Cadillac and on my Trenton G6
which I have photographed in front of
this awesome place along with an
outstanding review because I love it and
I recommend everybody do that it's like a
soul place. Anyway, my buddy's going. And
one more time on your name?Chris. Chris.
Well, I'm on...
It's badassI'm on a mission, and this is
a soul quest, but you can see us at
Clearwater Cruise... I hope you
succeed on your mission. Thank you, sir.
I hope you succeed on your mission.
Thank you. Whatever, whatever it might
be. Well, I'm trying to promote great
businesses. I mean I'm literally trying
to promote great businesses. I'm really
grateful for this place because it
literally, John in particular, Jan
in particular helped me tremendously
and I am very grateful for all that he's
done for me as one of the very best
mechanics that I know in this great land
and I'm gonna keep on saying it and I
hope you have a great day Chris, right?
Awesome! Huh
Thank you guys, we'll be right back.
We did go right back, by the way, and we
solved our problem, and he was so
awesome. And this is that, but
I'm a long time customer and dog park
friend.
In a previous life we were, um
I don't know.
So, this was a short walk. Sorry it got
really quiet here, but it does look
really cool, you knowLike, I
just really wanted to get this. It was so
much fun. It was just such an awesome
experience. Just out of the blue, we got
locked out of the truck. At first I was
really frustrated, and then I realized
that we had the perfect Harold and
Kumar adventure to have with each
other. And And we've been friends for a
long time. Do you know Ben also from the
park?You know Ben from the
park also. That
is so awesome, man.
See?I'm telling you, we have
so much karmic energy, bro.
Woo! Huh
I think we go like this way. Huh
Good afternoon.
Huh What
an awesome adventure. Harold and
Cubar go to White Castle.
What?Is this
not fun or what?It is
fun. It's total blast.
Ohh
All right, I don't want to stop the fun
here. Let's-- I am going to stop it for a
second. That was a great take. We'll be
back in a second, actually, I guess. OK,
bye.
All right, OK, now we're crossing the
walk here. Be careful, whoa, whoa, howdy,
howdy,
ho, ho, ho, all right. All right, thank
you.
Ah
And we are very good looking, by the way,
duhLike we're better looking than they
are, actually. Who?
Heldon Kumar. I
know I'm better looking than that. Come
on now. Huh
Anyhow, are we going to take this?Nah.
Uh
It is definitely warm out here.
And I'm glad you were paying attention in
break in class, because I missed it.
Break in class, class.
We're not going to break the glass. We're
going to break in, and that's the glass.
And you are paying attention to Ben,
which I wasn't because I'm manic, because
I had to figure out how to turn this in.
But man, it's so awesome, because I have
like about a million times more energy
right now. This is way better than a
workout. And we're out here in the middle
of everywhere,
and we get to see all these people out
here. How
are you guys today?What's
up?All right.
Okay. So the quest
continues, and right now we're out along
Route 60 here in
Clearwater in front of the Starbucks
coffee drive-through.
And the Seneca across the street, we
usually call that the Haji or
Habib store in honor of
our Middle Eastern uh
people that come here and set up shop
pretty much. Oh wow, look at this
wrap on this Tesla right here.
The Chanel group, look at that.
Alright, there you go. Uh, there's
Shinaga. Anyway.
Woo! Okay.
I gotta catch up with the med.
What a great day. What a
great day. Ah
All right, that's a nice Cadillac. Very
nice. It is a little large.
All right.
Hello, everyone.
Huhohh
I'm glad I still have that tooth there.
It hurts like a motor figure these days.
Alright, getting a call from
Commander-in-Chief, the Fifth Element.
Alright, let's see what will happen next.
Hey, are strange things put into Circle K?
No.
My name's Ken, by the way.
Hi, George. Well, we're
locked out of the USS Enterprise Soul
Van 1.
But we do have tools to enable
or facilitate access back
to the internal uh
workings of the ship, as it were.
And we are now about to get back in
to the Soul Van 1. What, one more name on
your, one more time on your name?
George. George, I want to say, I only got
a little bit of you. If you're one,
sorry, this goes on to my show. It's
called... Huh
What class of ship?It is
the Excursion class. It's the
Soul Fleet. It's the predecessor to the
Starfleet. Okay, but I've got to
go back there before he breaks it, all
right?Have a blessed day.
All right.
Pause. OK. Hmm
Yeah, we're going to have to use a
different door than this one, by the way.
We have to use the passenger door. Why?
Because I don't have a thing on this
side. Where's the windows?HuhWhere's the
window switch?Right here. This one?
Yeah. OK, we need to use this. That's it.
Open the window. Let's
hook it up. Huh
Right here.
Right there. Do you see it right there?
Yeah. This is so awesome.
Harold and Gomar go
to Walmart. We did it
together, huh? Well, our men and Ken go
to Walmart.
WOOOO!!! Let's go over and give them
some money. Well, we'll go back there
right now, no matter
what. Hi, buddy. Come here, man. Come
here, man.
I'm gonna be cool. You're not so
slobbery, buddy.
Hi, buddy.
Well, we'll
do that later. Right now, we're gonna get
this stuff put up.
Magadip! What a fun
adventure. But we
did get back in the van. It was going to
cost $80 from a lock spit and then I
would have to do a claim or something and
that would be $100 and this was
$10. Woo!
Thank you goodness gracious and thank you
teamwork because we had awesome teamwork.
I lost my cool for a little bit so I'm
really sorry toAhmed about
I was frustrated because I thought
everybody knew that you never leave a
vehicle running ever
if the keys are in the ignition unless
you put a window down.
No our feeling. We had a lot of fun
and really solidified a lot of really
awesome soul threads including Ben
at John's Auto Care because we all knew
each other. That's a real connection.
Huh, they're nice and cold compared to
out here. They're like veritably
freezing. All
right, so take your time. Huh
I didn't take it.
One moment. Missing a bottle of water. We
will find it.
We made an adventure out of it. We made
an adventure out of it. It was awesome.
It was a total freaking soul adventure.
And And it was awesome and we're gonna go
back to talk to Ben real quick. He'd been
super cool and like like
We both independently know Ben. Anyways.
All right. OK. So
that was our Soul Adventure. And then I
really wanted to pull up real quick Kevin
at Radioactive Car Audio. I think I have
some pictures from there. I wanted to
bring up some stuff because I was telling
Kevin from Radioactive Car Audio that I
would talk about them because I was
supposed to take the Soul Van in there to
get an inverter placed. And I wasn't able
to because the Solvans wind deflector
screens needed repaired.
Unfortunately, the people at Safelight
don't know how to jump a vehicle at 7:00
o'clock in the morning or their jump
device didn't work. So we had to take the
van back on Saturday at 3:00 o'clock to
get the deflector screen replaced for the
third time. And we left it there until
Thursday, which is the reason why the
battery went dead because anyway, it
needs a new battery probably.
So that's a lot of info. Real quick,
we're going to see if we can get some
footage of radioactive car audio. And
also, some other
cool stuff here before we go. So
also, we have a really awesome
playlist. So I'm going to pull up one of
those songs real quick, actually, while
I look for something. So let's pull up
one of our songs from our playlist here.
We're going to go back to
uh playlist. Let's listen to Pissed
the Curaleaf Dispensary Closed
Early. And let's just say that
The Fix was me.
The Fix was me. All right, so we're going
to go ahead and listen to Pissed the
Curaleaf Dispensary Closed Early.
And I wrote this song for them and I love
them. Katrina. Rebecca!
Hi, Rebecca!
Listen when people like, pay attention to
this. You're kind of a block.
Ohh
I'm sorry... Why did
I fix that?Alright.
Hunt the horn, yeah, I'm
right around the door But they locked it
up tight like they don't need more I'll
get this down. I got a semi-char mic
down. So why am I trippin' if they don't
give a damn Baby, I'm trippin', but that
ain't mine Took a while to get it up. 15
minutes. Why should I care, they ain't
really no bones Guess on me, I got the
late, I know But it's frustrating as
hell, but the kind of don't show Aw, man,
that messed it up.
I'm out here
wondering What's the fix?
That's a great song. I highly
recommend you jam out to it when you go
to Curling. We already know
that one. All right, we're going to go
ahead and look in our photo album real
quick for anything related to...
Ah, Radioactive.
Oh, there's my favorite couple.
Doctors Randi and Adonica Howard-Brown,
who had me beat up and thrown in jail.
Misunderstanding, no hard feelings, guys.
If you ever want to hang out, just give
me a call.
727-656-4443.
Feel free, give me a call, say hello. I'd
love to hang out sometime. Thank you
for a ride as we pass by.
Anyway, not feelies, guys. Come on.
Oh, oh, oh, oh,
okay. We're trying to find that. Let's
see if we can find it this way.
In this riot, spirit sleep
The journeythey
don't say it Rides like a Cadillac for
nothing we thrive Awesome Cadillac right
there From Harpo Springs to the
Cadillac CTS they don't say it
Rides like a Cadillac for nothing we
thrive From Tarpon Springs to St.
Pete Shore In our elegant rides
we explore Feels
race beneath the sky All right, let's
pause the music
Cadillac for nothing. We
are humming.
All right?
All right, we'll pause that for a moment.
We're gonna go back over. I really wanted
to show this off real quick. So this is
the Episcopal Church of the Ascension in
downtown Clearwater. And I'm a huge fan
of like everything
Tartaria is awesome. And
this right here, this Church of the
Ascension is so
exquisitely beautiful on the
outside. I can hardly wait to
attend service here. I'm so looking
forward to it. Hopefully they won't
trespass me when I
politely and penitently
enter that beautiful
structure and listen to what must be a
most amazing pipe organ and an
amazing experience. Look at
that flower there, the Church
of Iesus flower, this structure.
is incredible.
Ohh If it ever
loads. Okay, let's
see that. Maybe we'll look at that
another day because all it is
is a drive-by. So I got it there
and I got it there and you can see it's
just beautiful. And those stained glass
windows are amazing.
Anyhow, so I did take a little tour
around there. um
And that was the chip with the Med there.
And we had a nice little,
couple of nice things. I won't pull that
up right now 'cause we're talking about
radioactive car audio here. So this is
our, let's see if we can find
radio.
There you go. Let's see what we got. So
this is what we got, I think. I don't
really have any video there, umm
but I've been there a bunch and they did
a really great job on my subwoofer in the
Cadillac. I mean, I could more highly
recommend Kevin and his
expert team of
installers. He's been in business there
forever. He is an institution,
he's awesome, he's fun, he's reasonable.
and they just do awesome work.
And I just love hanging out with him and
the gang there whenever I get the chance.
I'm not saying go there and hang out, but
he really actually does like hanging out
and talking and and everything. So thank
you, Kevin. I look forward to seeing you
soon to get that inverter
uh installed properly in the back of the
solar van so that our subwoofer can
properly project itsholy
frequencies of loving kindness
out to the world. Thank you, Kevin.
We love
radioactive car audio. They are
so awesome. Anyway, just
got to give them super shout out. All
right, and they did a great job on the
subwoofer. And you can hear the subwoofer
all the time. As you know, in in
our videos, we have this awesome thing.
Here's going to court, by the way. Look
at the super hotty. Anyway,
she's like, ahShe
was frustrated. She's super hot.
She's the Fifth Element. That wasn't,
anyway, my Fifth Element. All right.
Okay, so now we talked about the Safe
Light, and I also wanted to give more
shout outs to my
favorite
vape shop, Strange Clouds. And
there's another vape shop I go to
regularly, which I'll give a shout out to
separately because they're awesome also.
But I just love Strange Clouds because
it's just so much fun to go into it.
Um Also,
real quick, we had like a really great,
awesome experience. I want to show this
one thing. This was actually
serendipitously shot, meaning I did not
press the button. You can see my hand is
clearly on the steering wheel. And we
were going around to pantry to pantry
here. And I'll show just a little glimpse
of this because I'm trying to keep the
runtime on this one short. But
this is a scene where I'm actually-- this
was not taken by me.
Ah
We're going to try to download it. I've
got it downloading right there. Ah,
here it comes. I
need it anyhow, and I think I made a
better version of it.
Now I'm looking in my captures directory.
I want to see if I have
that particular
All right, guys, hold on. Wait, I was
just... Okay, these are the secret
archives. I can't show 'cause this is one
that supposedly went on the deep end and
actually had a samadhi experience. Ohh
Responded. A really serious samadhi
experience. Enjoy. Genuinely. And when
she's... And she's... Okay. Um..
Greeting. Um..
Go on here.
real quick and then go back home and drop
off and go to the bathroom and go back to
the dog park. Is that okay, Fifth Element?
Yeah, yeah, yeahNo, I'm speaking to the
Fifth Element. Um, yeah, but you need to
ask, you might not. I understand
what you're saying. Do you want
to go see something beautiful real quick?
Ohh Is it open?Do you need it?
Alright, so this is the one, anyway.
Alright. so van um
let's see it
oh there was already there
Real quick and then go back home and drop
off to go to the bathroom and go back to
the dog park. Is that OK?Fit the element?
Yeah.
Hey there, I want to take.
All right. Okay. So I got
carried away, and I made a video, and I
wasn't even anything. So you
just sat with me for a few minutes. I
should probably edit that out, but I
don't ever edit this stuff out. So I made
this video, which is
honestly truthful. I did
not press the record button.
I... did not... press the
record button.
Who pressed the record button?
Go real quick and then go back home and
drop off the... go to the bathroom and go
back to the dog park. Is that okay?Fifth
Element?No, no, noNo, I'm speaking to the
Fifth Element. Um, yeah, but you need to
ask him. He might not. We were on a
mission of philanthropy of mercy.
Ohh Is it open?And this
Soul Van one, USS Enterprise. Okay,
let's do it. All right. Soul Van. If I
open somebody else up, it uh, asked me
to. Activate subwoofer!
Ready, player! Everyone!
Everyone gets an angel! Go
back home and drop off. All right. Go to
the bathroom and go back to the club
park. Is that
okay?And let's go back here. And we'll go
back to channel content. And we have to
look at Maximus Reximus as our pal.
Oh ohh my goodness, look at that baby.
Please like this one. Watch this one, I
like it. Please. Pretty please.
You okay?He
is so cute. We love this dog so
much.
Oh, so awesome. Look at that. I love this
little guy. I love that little
guy. I love that little guy. I
love him. I love my buddies.
He's such a great pal. He's my
grandfather, Harry. Anyway, we
always watch something on YouTube. We are
getting a lot more like... What's
wrong?What happened?Meditative
selections going.
All right, so we did that and we want to
get back to, and so that's Clearwater
Cruising Ministries, of which I am a
contributor. And my lovely Fifth
Element is the
proprietors of--
all right. We want to go back here.
If you're still with me, thank you. All
right. And so here is a little bit of
our
journey inside of
the pantry real quick. And
we do actually sometimes use this because
we are at the very edge of economic
sustenance right now. I'm having a hard
time with like my bandwidth here today.
It's the reason why I'm not streaming.
I'm actually recording this and uploading
it. OK, that's not going to work
probably right now. And I don't feel like
digging deeper. But
that was our pantry expedition.
Um, and this is the taco,
not the taco stand, but the
most beautiful sunset
ever with the most awesome,
awesome um
Southwest egg roll stand, egg roll truck.
They're around the area, but they were
there this night. And I really wish this
would load.
AhSo I dump
them off my phone, and then they upload
into Google Photos. And usually, they
load pretty instantaneously. Maybe what's
going on. Let's see.
Davidas Music. Oh, love
Davidas. I am Davidas.
And he is on YouTube.
And this guy's a local artist, and I love
him. UmBut
we got to check them out on YouTube here.
Gotta close out some stuff.
All right, so we closed out some stuff
here. This is my private Discord clone in
case anybody's been interested. I
actually wrote this, and this is kind of
a predecessor to this Angel OS in a
way. This is a very
sophisticated Discord clone, I might add.
That also includes real-time video
communication that you can actually--
if I wasn't using my camera already, it
would work. And I haven't gotten my other
camera going here. But yeah, this is
completely awesome in real
time. And it runs on free
software here. And right now,
the last thing we were doing
All right. We were trying to sell some
philanthropy and some other stuff around
the area. I think the main thing that we
communicated and we're running up to like
52 minutes or 53 minutes and
53 is the new answer to the life universe
and everything. I wanted to show some
Strange Cloud stuff from earlier time. So
main thing, I gave a shout out to Bianca
from the Strange Clouds that we visited
before and super grateful for that
awesome in the bait, six milligram
slushy flavor. That's so awesome. I love
it. When I still vape, I'm trying to
quit. And I didn't even vape once in this
entire thing. All I can say is if you
stuck with me, thank you. um If
you have anything you want, I have tons
of stuff I want to share, but the main
thing was just that we had a great day
with Harold and Kumar went to White
Castle, only it was Ahmed and Kenneth
went to John's Auto Service
and Walmart. All right, guys.
Thanks for watching. Like and subscribe.
Seriously, and have a blessed day.